Register of the S. I. Hayakawa papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington Office, Administrative/Legislative Files (Boxes 1-265)
  - Banking (Box 54)
    - Banking
    - C.A.R.E.
    - S. 1720/1721, Banking revisions and FDIC consolidation
    - S. 2226, Emergency Mortgage Interest Payment Act
    - Savings and loans acquisitions
    - S. 1720/1721/1703, Financial Restructuring Acts
    - S. 2465, Appropriations for Securities and Exchange Commission
    - Securities and Exchange Commission
    - U.S. Bonds
    - Savings Bonds and marketable securities
    - Credit unions
    - Repurchase agreements
    - Renegotiations Board
    - Regulation Q
    - Regulation D
    - NOW (Box 56)
    - New York Stock Exchange
    - National Development Bank
    - Mortgage Revenue Bonds
    - Mortgage loans
    - Federal Reserve Policy
    - Federal Reserve accountability
    - Federal Home Loan Bank Board
    - Federal Reserve Board
    - EPAC development
    - Credit unions
    - CAL-VET/Mortgage Subsidy Bonds
    - Yamaha - Brunswick
  - Commerce, Science, Transportation
    - Airline deregulation
      - Comments in support
      - Comments in opposition (Box 57)
      - L.A.-London, Bermuda 11
    - Amtrak
    - Bottle Bill
    - BUY AMERICAN ACT - letter to Administrator Bowers
    - H.R. 11733, Federal aid to surface transportation
    - Communication television
    - Brake standard
    - Pro 55 mph speed limit
    - Con 55 mph speed limit
    - 55 mph speed limit (Box 58)
    - S. 3073, The Federal-Aid Highway Act, 1978
    - Insurance
    - ICC Van regulations
    - Mass transit
    - Mass transit (Box 59)
    - Metric Board, nominations
    - NASA
      - General
      - Programs
      - Syncom IV
    - University of California, Alameda/Berkeley/NASA
    - FY, 79
      - Authorization
      - Appropriation
    - TAXI-JITNEY BILL
      - Correspondence
      - Articles (Box 60)
    - Taxi data for cities
    - Responses on Jitney amendment
    - Jitneys - mass transit
    - TAXI-JITNEY
    - Trucking Deregulation, Description/Analysis/Publication (Box 61)
    - Weather, general
    - Commerce
      - California World Fair 1988
      - FTC
      - Shared monopoly legislation
      - Lawnmower regulations
      - 1984 Summer Olympics
      - FTC used car rules
    - Communications
      - Close captioning
      - FCC & ICC Commissioner re-education
      - International Record Carrier Act
      - HITEL network (Box 62)
      - Goldwater Cable Bill, S. 2172
      - Space
      - Weather, fruit frost
    - Transportation: Air, Auto, Highway, Rail
      - ADAP
      - Airline deregulation
      - Bakersfield Kern City Airport
      - FAA
      - Drunk Driving
      - Passive Restraint Systems/Airbags
      - Motor vehicle cost savings authorization
      - Century Freeway
      - 55 MPH
      - Roger Johnson on "55"
      - Alaska RR giveaway
      - Senate Rail Caucus
      - France, US Rail Congress
      - Railroads
      - Southern Pacific RR
      - Uniform Motor Vehicle Standards Act
      - S. 1390, Trucking Safety
    - Mass Transit
      - Mass Transit S. 2720
      - BART (Box 63)
      - Cable Cars
      - S. 2696, Hayakawa Ridesharing
      - S. 1914, Hayakawa Sabotage Bill (Box 64)
  - Environment
    - Environment memos
    - S. 18, Orange Coast Park
    - S 705, small tracts
    - S. 842, RARE II
    - S. 842, RARE II (Box 65)
    - National Release Language, wilderness
    - S. 1117, Mt. Shasta (Box 66)
    - S. 1187, boundary lines
    - S. 1242, El Dorado National Forest
    - S. 1584, Cranston, California Wilderness
    - S. 2061, Moynihan-Mathias
    - S. 2418, Luiseno Indians
    - S. 2684, Santa Margarita Dam
    - S. 2801, oil and gas leases
    - S. 2805, timber leases (Box 67)
    - S. 2811, Tuolumne
    - HR 2475, Mono County Land Exchange
    - Air Quality, Vehicle Inspection Maintenance (S. 52)
    - Clean Air Act
      - General
      - Committee
    - Clean Water Reauthorization (Box 68)
    - Earthquakes
    - Hazardous wastes
    - Noise pollution
      - General
      - Railroad regulations
    - Oil spill liability
    - Otay Mesa Border Station
  - Fish and Wildlife
    - Wild and scenic rivers
    - Convention on Trade and Endangered Species
    - Endangered Species
      - General
      - Bobcat
    - Fish and Wildlife Coordination Act
    - Fisheries
    - Klamath River Fisheries
    - Marine Mammal Protection Act
    - New Hogan Fisheries (Box 69)
    - Pacific Fishery Management Council
    - Rough Fish
    - Tuna problem
    - Whales
    - National Resources Advisory Committee
  - Public Lands
    - Alaska lands
    - Big Sur (Box 70)
    - Big Sur (Box 71)
    - California wilderness
    - Channel Islands
    - Harvey's Fishing Hole
    - Los Angeles Juniper Hills
    - Los Padres oil leases
    - Mineral King
    - Mono Lake
    - Orange Coast National Urban Park
    - Plumas Forest
    - Redwood National Park Employee Protection Plan (Box 72-73)
    - Redwood Park Program
    - Redwood articles, LA Times
    - Santa Monica Mountains National Recreation Area
    - Shasta/Trinity National Forest (Box 74)
    - Sweeney Ridge
  - Policy & Management - Lands
    - Land use
    - Timber contracts
    - Economic Development Administration
    - Environmental Protection Agency personnel
    - FEMA - Imperial Country
  - Indians of California
  - Ocean Policy
    - National Ocean Policy Review
    - Desalinization
  - Water Policy
    - Acreage limitation
      - General
      - Family Farm Liberation Act
    - California Water Commission, flood control
    - Water quality
      - General
      - Drinking water
    - Water policy
    - Water rights
  - Water Projects (Box 75)
    - Contra Costa
    - Lake Almanor
    - Oceanside Beach erosion
    - Redondo Beach, King Harbor
    - San Jacinto River Levee
  - Energy
    - S. 506, Pauley
    - S. 506, Pauley (Box 76)
    - S. 326, Divorcement, Metzenbaum
    - S. 498, Passive Solar Tax Credits
    - S. 750, Industrial Energy Security Tax Incentive
    - S. 875, Palo Verde
    - S. 1280, Emergency Partnership Act
    - S. 1288, Commercial Business Energy Tax Credit Act
    - S. 1503, Standby Petroleum Allocation Act (Box 77)
    - S. 1662, Nuclear Waste
    - S. 2773, Alaskan oil exports
    - S. 2773, Alaskan oil exports (Box 78)
    - Energy Advisory Committee
    - Energy
    - Energy (Box 79)
    - Coal
      - General
      - Coal synfuels
    - Gasoline
      - Allocation system
      - Poor people, gas
    - Natural Gas
      - Home heating oil
      - Natural Gas Decontrol - ban, 1990
      - Natural Gas Incremental Pricing
      - LNG
      - Canadian Gas Pricing
    - Nuclear (Box 80)
      - General
      - Clinch River
      - Diablo Canyon
      - Fusion (Box 81)
      - Rancho Seco
      - Edward Teller
      - Three Mile Island
    - Oil
      - General
      - Export oil residual oil from California (Box 82)
      - Heavy oil
      - Elk Hills (Box 83)
      - Import fee
      - OPEC
      - Leasing
      - Outer Continental Shelf Five Year Plan (Box 84)
      - OCS Sale #48
      - OCS Sale #53
      - OCS Sale #68 (Box 85)
      - OCS Sale #73
      - Strategic Petroleum Reserve
      - Windfall profits tax (Box 86)
    - Solar
      - General
      - Barstow
      - Monticello Power Plant
      - Thermal (Box 87)
    - California Power Companies & Special Projects
      - Hoover Dam
      - Lawrence Livermore Laboratory
      - Palo Verde Irrigation Hydro Project
      - Thermionics
  - Environment - Early Years
    - Endangered species
    - Energy and natural resources, Endangered AM Wilderness Act of, 1977 (Box 88)
    - H.R. 3454, Endangered Wilderness Bill
  - Foreign Relations
    - Africa
      - SIH Africa trip, cables, letters, 1978, 1982
      - Letters from SIH
      - Letters to SIH
      - Liberian Coup - SIH letter to Secretary Vance
      - S. Con. Res. 98 - Liberia
      - S. Con. Res. 8 - Rhodesian Observers
      - Lifting sanctions on Rhodesia/Zimbabwe, SIH letters
      - Rhodesia (Box 89)
        - Foreign Relations Committee background
        - SIH statements, columns, letters
        - S. Res. 500 - Zimbabwe resolution, 1982
        - Mungazi case - Zimbabwe
    - East Asia (Box 90)
      - East Asia trip proposal, 1982
      - Asian trip, SIH letters, memos, cables, remarks, 1981
      - East Asian trip, 1980
      - Aid to Cambodia
      - China Claims Project, 1979-1980
      - China Seminar - SIH chairman, committee report, 4/82
      - General (Box 91)
      - SIH testimony chair East Asia Subcommittee
      - S. 1668 - SIH/Cranston IRAP amendment, 11/79
      - Japan trade issues, SIH letters, 1980
      - SIH Japan trip, 11/78
      - Japan defense - committee hearings, 1982
      - Japan sub accident, 1981
      - Treaty of Kiribati - SIH letter/background
      - Korea - SIH meeting with Korean ambassador, 1981
      - Robert Palmer, Ambassador to Malaysia - SIH comments, remarks
      - Indochina refugees - SIH/Committee, 1980
      - S.E. Asia drug hearings, 1982
      - South Korea centennial, 1982
      - SIH letter to President Reagan - F-5E sales to Taiwan
      - Taiwan resolutions, SIH/background, 1979-1980
      - Taiwan arms sales, 1981
      - Taiwan/US relations, SIH/Committee report, 1979
      - Taiwan Relations Act - SIH/Committee, 1979
      - Thailand
      - Vietnam
      - Soviet dissident letters consigned, 1980
    - Europe (Box 92)
      - H. Con. Res. 200 - Baltic States Resolution
      - NATO troop reductions - Foreign Relations Committee, 12/82
      - SALT II - overview of SALT process, Foreign Relations Committee
    - USSR (Box 93-96)
      - SALT II
      - Moscow trip, SIH
      - Soviet dissident letters, 1979-1980
      - Soviet Jews letters, 1982
      - Soviet gas pipeline, State response, 1981
      - Siberian Seven letter to Reagan, 1980
      - S.J. Res. 135 - Religious Freedom in USSR, SIH correspondence
    - Western Hemisphere (Box 97)
      - Alaska Oil bill, 1982
      - Caribbean Basin Initiative - SIH/Committee, 1982
      - Chile - SIH letter on inter-American naval exercise
      - S.J. Res. 158 - Symms letter on Cuba
      - Cuba - educational exchange letter from SIH
      - El Salvador certification, Committee, 1982
      - Falklands - Vicar of Bray, 1982
      - Mexico
        - Illegal aliens - letter and committee, 1970-1980
        - SIH letters, columns - trade/aliens, 1980/1981
        - Ambassador Nava background - Committee (Box 98)
        - Background on establishing a bi-national commission
      - Nicaragua
        - Committee background
        - Foreign Assistance hearings/Committee, SIH letters
      - Panama Canal, 1979
      - Panama Canal, 1979 (Box 99)
      - Radio Marti, 1982 (Box 100)
    - Middle East (Box 101)
      - S. Con. Res. 45 - Rights of Afghan people, SIH letter to the President
      - Soviet Invasion of Afghanistan, 1980
      - S. Res. 142 - "Afghanistan Day", SIH cosponsor, 1982
      - Egypt - letter to SIH from Deputy PM and Minister of Defense, 11/82
      - Iran - SIH letter to PM Bazargan, 3/79
      - American Sovereignty Protection Act, background, SIH papers
      - Camp David Accords, SIH/Committee, 1979
      - Jordan - letter from Hussein and background report, 3/82
      - Lebanon - SIH letter to President, Foreign Relations Comm., 1981
    - International Organizations
      - AID - SIH letters
      - ICA - SIH letters
      - IMET - SIH amendment, Fulbright (Box 102)
      - Law of the Sea Treaty
      - Sugar Agreement
    - Foreign Assistance Appropriations
      - Supplemental Appropriation - For. Assistance, 1983
      - For. Assistance Approp., SIH committee, 1981
      - For. Assistance Approp., SIH committee, 1979-1980
    - Miscellaneous Legislation (Box 103)
      - Dr. Bracker memos
      - Briefing materials
      - Committee agendas
      - Committee Budget, 1980
      - Correspondence with Percy
      - Daily News Summary
      - East Asia Subcommittee agendas
      - Foreign income tax
      - Foreign Missions Act
      - Foreign Relations Authorization (Box 104)
      - Holdridge
      - Jurisdiction with Armed Services Committee
      - LeFever
      - Schultz
      - State Department Authorization
      - US/UK Tax Treaty
      - US/UK Tax Treaty (Box 105)
  - Foreign Relations/Defense Files
    - Special Projects/Cases
      - Americans in Cuba
      - Bahai cases
      - Bishop Tutu
      - Yuri Bodzyo
      - Viktor Brailovsky
      - Otto Burgdorf
      - California Nickle Corporation
      - Henry Chang
      - Coalition for Peace Through Strength
      - Michael Coyne
      - Dr. Dary
      - Ralph DePaul
      - Bill Devitt (Box 106)
      - Djordevich
      - Foreign Claims
      - Fort Ord
      - Alex Guttman
      - Rikizo Hirano
      - Bruce Hopping
      - International Order of St. Hubert
      - Jean Kirkpatrick/UN
      - Dick Lupton
      - LA World Trade Annex
      - Marcu Case
      - Vasile Matei
      - John McManis
      - Michalkow
      - Eugene Miller
      - Herman Miller
      - National Semiconductor Corporation
      - National University NROTC
      - Natori case
      - Naval Hospital, San Diego (Box 107)
      - Nemoianu case
      - Nikita case
      - Ida Nudel
      - PRC cases
      - Harry Pascal referals
      - Peace Corps cases
      - Pieptea case
      - Posthauer
      - Pottl/Fuentes
      - Project Concern
      - Replies to Bucks
      - Romanian cases
      - Joe Rosenthal
      - Rus case
      - Sakharov, Andrei
      - Salvation Army Grant (Box 108)
      - Benedict Scott
      - Sivov case
      - Vladimir Slepak
      - Michael Smith
      - Soviet Jewry cases
      - Soviet cases
      - State buck replies
      - Swentek
      - Szostkowski
      - Maria Tiemkin
      - Vasile cases
      - Raoul Wallenberg
      - Willard Company
      - Wine
      - World Affairs Council
  - Defense Files
    - Legislation
      - FY82 Military Construction Authorization
      - DOD
        - Appropriation, 1982
        - Authorization, 1982
      - Military Construction Authorization and Appropriation FY, 1981
      - FY81 Military Procurement Authorization (Box 109)
      - DOD Procurement Appropriations FY, 81
    - Defense Policy Issues
      - Use of bacteria in San Francisco area by US Army
      - Bilateral Nuclear Arms Freeze
      - Nuclear
      - Chemical warfare
      - Defense jobs
      - MBFR negotiations
      - Navy Five Year Shipbuilding Plan
      - Navy Ship Repair in the Bay Area
      - Reagan Defense program
      - FR Hearings Reagan Strategic Package
      - Reagan TNF offer
      - Arms sales
      - Middle East Arms Sales
      - Arabsat
      - F-16's to Pakistan
      - Arms sales to Jordan
      - Arms sales to Venezuela
      - Arms sales to Saudi Arabia (Box 110)
      - Arms sales to Taiwan
    - POW/MIA (Box 111)
      - Miscellaneous
      - Armitage Hanoi visit
      - DOD information
      - Laos cases
      - SIH Laos resolutions, 10/82
      - SIH Laos trip, 8/81
      - House action
      - Interagency group
      - Johnny King case
      - League factbook
      - League newsletter
      - POW/MIA Recognition Day
      - Staff working group
      - TAM of the Month - Ann Griffith
    - Manpower/Benefits
      - The draft
      - Fire fighters/sec.
      - Handicapped in military physical standards
      - Housing
      - McCarty vs. McCarty, S. 1453
      - Military pay
      - Military Traffic Management
      - National Youth Service
      - Registration
      - H.J. Res. 51, Registration bill
      - Women in the service
    - Defense Systems (Box 112)
      - Ammunition M509 ICM 811
      - B-1 (Y 77 Recission on, 5/6)
      - B-77 (FUFO bomb)
      - Battleship Iowa
      - C-5B/747's Jackson amendment
      - C-17 Airlift (Airforce)
      - F-16 (AF fighter)
      - F-18 (Navy)
      - KC-10 Tanker (AF)
      - Minuteman III
      - MRASH (Med. range air to surf.)
      - Multiple launch Rocket Systems (Army)
      - Neutron bomb
      - P-3C
      - S-3A Navy Lockheed
      - Surface effects ship (Navy)
      - TACAN (AF)
      - TACFIRE (Army)
      - Tactical Command and Control Air Force
      - TAK-X- Navy
      - V-STOL Harrier
    - Military Branches (Box 113)
      - Air Force
      - Army
      - Defense Logistics Agency
      - National Guard
      - Naval Reserves
      - Navy
    - California bases
      - Beale Air Force Base
      - City of Bell - Land purchase
      - China Lake Naval Weapons Center
      - Defense Language Institute (DLI)
      - Mare Island Naval Shipyard
      - McClellan Air Force Base
      - Navy housing - Long Beach, LA
      - Norton Air Base
      - San Diego County
      - Tierrasanta Naval Housing
      - Vandenberg Air Force Base
    - Defense contractors (Box 114)
      - Applied Technology
      - Boeing
      - Bethlehem Steel Shipyard
      - C & R
      - DWR - Small Business
      - Garret Corporation
      - General Dynamics
      - Hughes
      - Lockheed
      - McDonnell Douglas
      - Norris Industries
      - Northrop
      - Rockwell
      - Rohr Industries
      - Teledyne (Box 115)
      - Todd Shipyard
      - TRW
  - Governmental Affairs
    - Consumer Protection Agency
    - GAO
      - Marketing orders
      - NIMR
    - GSA
      - General
      - Contract Awards
      - Hamilton Air Force Base
      - Santa Clara County Jail
      - Yerba Buena
    - Intervenor Funding
    - Department of Education
      - Dismantling
      - '78-'79
      - S. 991
    - District of Columbia
      - Appropriations
        - General
        - Convention Center
      - Home Rule Charter
    - Lobby Reform
      - Lobby Disclosure Act
      - Lobby reform bills
    - Privacy
      - Farmland
      - Federal Assistance Reform
    - Sunset
      - 96th
      - 95th
  - Rules (Box 116)
    - Rules and Administration
      - Franking
      - Hart Resolution #44
      - Museum: African Art
      - Presidential Nominating Process Commission
      - Senate Rules changes
    - Federal Election Commission (FEC)
      - General
      - Campaign contribution reform
      - Public Finance S. 926
      - Universal Voter Registration S. 1072
      - National Right to Work
  - Major issues (Box 117)
    - Beginners wage
      - General
      - Social Bonus
    - Davis-Bacon
    - Polling bills
      - Early Media Projections S. 55-58
      - Simultaneous Voting Hours
  - Labor (Box 118)
    - DOL: Surplus labor areas
    - EEOC: Slate nomination
    - ERISA
      - 96th
      - PL 96-364
    - Hughes, Laddie
    - Labor
      - OFCCP
      - Gallant Eagle #82
    - Longshoremen
      - Workers
      - S. 1182 (hearing)
    - NLRB
      - Betra
      - Truesdale nomination
      - Van de Water nomination
    - National Mediation Board: Republic Air
    - Railroad Retirement Act Amendments
    - Right to Work
    - Training for Jobs S. 2036
  - Housing & Urban Development (HUD)
    - Miscellaneous
    - Amador
    - Bishop Indian
    - Giant Step
    - Healy
    - Holden Street
    - Japanese American Heritage Center
    - Lutheran Center
    - Nelson
    - Orange County
      - Environmental Management
      - Housing
    - Quechan
    - Sakkis vs. Oakland
    - Victoria Gardens
    - Walnut Ranch (Box 119)
    - Willowbrook
  - Legislation
    - Sponsor/Cosponsor
      - American Sovereignty Protection Act S. 66
      - Davis-Bacon S. 3
      - Debt Collection S. 1249
      - ERISA S. 1748
      - GSA: Criminal Justice Facility S. 1422
      - Page Board: S. 2742
      - Polling Bills S. 55-58
      - Regulatory Reduction S. 890
      - A-76 S. 2278
      - Retainage S. 1782
      - Small Business Sec. 8 (a) S. 1947
      - White House Conference on Productivity
      - Appropriation bills
    - Inactive (Box 120)
      - Appropriation bills
      - Budget
      - Commission for More Effective Government
      - D.C.: Sexual Assault
      - Delinquent Payments
      - Farmland Protection
      - Training for Jobs S. 2036
      - Railroad Strike
    - Human Resources - 95th Congress
      - Dr. Backer memos - human resources
      - Human Resources Committee - Aging
      - Aging Sub. 1170, Commodities Program (Box 121)
      - Education Subcommitte Testimony
      - Education Subcommittee
        - S. 602
        - S. 778
      - CETA, Employment Subcommittee
      - Employment Subcommittee, S. 50, Humphrey-Hawkins
      - Labor Subcommittee (Box 122)
        - S. 995
        - S. 717, Mine Safety
        - S. 1871, Fair Labor Standards Act
        - Labor Law Reform
  - Aging, Refugees, Miscellaneous Issues, Social Security (Box 123)
    - Affirmative Action
    - SIH comments - aging
    - Aging-Housing demos - SIH statement
    - Elderly as victims of crime (violent)
    - Aging - OAA, 1981
    - Older American Employment Week, 1981
    - OAA, 1981
    - Aging - pensions, 1981
    - Aging - Western Gerontological Society
    - Aging employment hearing - SIH testimony, 4/82
    - Crime, 1981
    - Briefing book, 1980 (Box 124)
    - Aging - White House Conference
    - Day care
      - General
      - Survey
    - National Closed Caption TV Month
    - CROP
    - Domestic violence
      - Prevention and Services Act
      - 1978
      - Conference report
    - California Refugee Shortfall
    - Refugee Ed.
      - Hearing - SIH testimony, 3/82
      - Funding cut, '81
      - Impact Aid, 1979
      - - SIH amendment to ESEA, July, 1978
      - Amendments to extend Indochinese Refugee Children Assistance Act authorization
    - Refugees
      - Welfare
      - Indochinese refugees
      - Settlement and benefits statistics
      - Cash and medical assistance extension - committee amendment, 1978
      - Budget increase, SIH statement, 6/81
    - Merit Youth Awards by Congress - SIH co-sponsor, 95th Congress
    - Shriners - SIH statement, 1981 (Box 125)
    - San Bernardino Civic Light Opera
    - Special Projects, El Centro
    - Social Security
      - Legislation
      - SSI/Food stamp cash-out
      - Medicare deductible
      - Medicare - mental health benefits
      - Welfare
        - General
        - Child
      - Home Health Care
        - Bills
        - Co-sponsorship
      - Hospice Care, 1982
      - Health Maintenance Organizations
      - Alien abuses
      - General information
      - Co-sponsorship of Heinz Amendment to remove Social Security from the Budget
      - Percy S.S.I. abuses by aliens
      - Title IVD Social Security proposal
      - S. Res. 432 Taxing SS
      - Unemployment offset
      - Benefits to dead people
      - S. 2722 Prisoners on SS
      - Social Security H.R. 4331 Minimum Benefit
  - Health (Box 126)
    - Advisory Committee
    - Batten's Disease
    - DMSO, 96th Congress
    - El Arca Handicapped project in E. Los Angeles
    - Emergency Medical Services
    - FDA CA state toxic substances proposal, 1982
    - FDA drug lag, 1981
    - Food Safety Revision, S. 1442
    - Handicapped
      - Education, 1982
      - Pilots, ADD, 11/81
    - Health Maintenance Organizations (HMO)
    - Health Manpower Amendment, S. 2159
    - Hospitals, rural, overregulation
    - International Year of Disabled Persons
    - Koop nomination, 1981 (Box 127)
    - National Health Insurance (NHI)
    - Prisoners, research
    - Rigsbee, case, home health care
    - Saccharin
    - Teenage Pregnancy Bill, S. 2910
    - Wine labels
    - Memoranda to Amy, Mike and Press (Box 128)
    - Letters to co-sign or did co-sign "Dear Colleagues"
    - Dr. Wueschner
    - Meetings of the week
    - Berkeley Fulbright India Program
    - Film at Library of Congress
    - Rural community health care centers
    - Livingston Lysate Scott A-510 (Box 129)
    - Indian Health Services
    - Title X: Notification
    - Alcohol and drug abuse
    - Batten's disease
    - Dr. Taub's cruelty to animals
    - Office of Community Services
    - CSA